THOMAS GUERENA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER



EXPERIENCE

Spring - Summer, 2015

University Capstone Project (ffosbr.js)

Technical Lead / Software Engineer Collaborated with Mozilla to create a backup and restore utility library for Firefox OS devices. Integration into OS forthcoming.

2014 - 2015

iServeLife

Back-end Architect / Front-end Engineer Web application connecting users to non-profit volunteer opportunities based on personal interests. UI/UX design.

2013 - 2014

Kokonect

Full-stack Engineer

Interactive campus map application for Lewis & Clark College.

UI/UX design. Managed client feedback and test groups.

2012 - 2013

Vernier Software

Software Intern

Built the Labquest 2 updater, still being used by thousands of customers. Performed software maintenance and research.

ABOUT ME

I'm Thomas Guerena

a Software Engineer in Portland, Oregon.

I have 3 years of experience as a javascript engineer. However, I have a boad spectrum of interests and abilities. I enjoy working with clients, designing applications as much as I do cryptography and AI (almost). Please read more about me on my website, thomasguerena.com.

EDUCATION

2010 - 2015

Computer Science

Porltand State University, Major

Mathematics

Portland State University, Minor

SKILLS

Javascript	
HTML5 / CSS3	
Unit Testing / CI	
NodeJS	
C/C++	
SQL	
NoSQL	
Java	
Python	
UI/UX Design	

TOOLS

Git	
NPM	
Grunt / Gulp	
Bower	
Yeoman	

CONTACT

5713 NE 13th Ave, Portland, Oregon, 97211

t: 1 541 921 8717

e: guerena.t@gmail.com

w: www.thomasguerena.com

facebook.com/thomas.guerena.9

@thomasguerena

REFERENCES

Joe Sauer

Supervisor - Vernier Software T: 1 503 690 9156 E: joesauer@yahoo.com

Ryan Bernstein

Capstone Project Leader T: 1 503 830 2007 E: rlb@pdx.edu

Margaret Adams

CEO Kokonect LLC T: 1 503 360 5542 E: margaret@simple.com